const qa = [
    { question : "What city is Jay-Z from?",
      answers :  [
        "Toronto;",
        "Brooklyn",
        "Chicago",
        "Los Angeles"
      ],
      correct : "Brooklyn"
    },
    { question : "What Kanye West last album title",
      answers :  [
        "Ye",
        "My Beautiful Dark Twisted Fantasy",
        "The Life of Pablo",
        "Yeezus"
      ],
      correct : "Ye"
    },
    { question : "What does OVO stand for?",
      answers :  [
        "Do right and kill every thing",
        "Octobers Very Own",
        "The six",
        "You Only Live Once"
      ],
      correct : "Octobers Very Own"
    },
    { question : "Who is Marshall Bruce Mathers",
      answers :  [
        "Machine Gun Kelly",
        "Action Bronson",
        "50 Cent",
        "Eminem",
      ],
      correct : "Eminem"
    },
    { question : "Which one of these is NOT a producer?",
      answers :  [
        "Damon Dash",
        "Timbaland",
        "Snoop Dog",
        "Dr Dre",
      ],
      correct : "Snoop Dog"
    },
    { question : "Which record label featured artists such as Dr. Dre, Tupac, and Snoop Dogg?",
      answers :  [
        "Death Row",
        "Jr. Mafia",
        "Rock-A-Fella",
        "The Dungeon Family"
      ],
      correct : "Death Row"
    },
    { question : "At what age did the Notorious BIG pass",
      answers :  [
        "20",
        "24",
        "30",
        "35"
      ],
      correct :
        "24"
    },
    { question : "Which rapper was NOT a member of Wu-Tang Clan?",
      answers : [
        "ODB",
        "Method Mans",
        "U-God",
        "Royce Da 5'9"
      ],
      correct : "Royce Da 5'9"
    },
    { question : "What was the name of Fresh Prince's DJ?",
      answers : [
        "King Coopa",
        "Funk Master Flex",
        "Jazzy Jeff",
        "Envy"
      ],
      correct: "Jazzy Jeff"
    },
    { question : "Which Nas song did Jay-Z sample for his song Dead Presidents?",
      answers : [
        "Made You Look",
        "If I Ruled The World",
        "One Mic",
        "The World is Yours"
      ],
      correct: "The World is Yours"
    }
  
  ]